spingo.com 2013-05-16

# Privacy Policy - SpinGo

SpinGo (SpinGo Solutions, LLC.) respects your right to privacy and understands the importance of protecting it. The privacy policy below details the measures taken by SpinGo to protect your privacy in connection with your use of SpinGo.com. This privacy policy is intended to help you understand how SpinGo collects and uses any personal information you choose to share.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please address them to privacy [at] spingo.com. You may also contact us by mail at 1234 North 900 East, Provo, UT, 84604.

SpinGo only collects personal information about you that you have knowingly chosen to disclose to us. We ask you to register or to provide personal information when you post an event to SpinGo.com. This information is required in order to verify the actuality of the event and will not be disclosed on the SpinGo site or calendars. If you choose not to share your personal information, your event submission may not be published on the SpinGo calendars. If you register with SpinGo.com or purchase event upgrades from us, you may automatically receive emails confirming your registration and/or purchase, providing you with the necessary information relating to the access or use of your registration and/or purchase. With the exception of the emails described in the preceding sentence, which are necessary to provide customer support and deliver products and services to you, _you will not receive email from SpinGo._

As with most websites, our web servers will also collect information about your visit, but this will not be personal information. This _information may include the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit._

Acceptance of Privacy Policy

By using SpinGo.com, you are accepting the practices set out in this privacy policy and in the terms of service. SpinGo reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. Any revisions made to this privacy policy to reflect changes in SpinGo.com will be posted on our site. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Should any changes be deemed unacceptable to you, you will cease to use SpinGo.com. Continued use of SpinGo.com shall be interpreted as acceptance of changes in the privacy policy.

Method of Information Collection

SpinGo uses a form for users to request information, submit events and purchase event upgrades or sponsorships. For that order form, we collect a user's contact information and necessary financial information to process the order (i.e. credit card number). Contact information from the order (including email) is used to deliver information from SpinGo. SpinGo may use third parties to accept and process orders and credit card purchases for services.

All communication on the internet takes place between pairs of IP Addresses. Our Web servers will log the IP address from which any connection is made. We may use these IP addresses to help diagnose technical problems or prevent abuse of our systems or other site users. Your IP address may also be used to gather aggregate demographic data and target advertisements accordingly.

A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your Web browser for record-keeping purposes and to help us provide better service to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject, or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. We use cookies to save your password (in an encrypted format) on your machine so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

The SpinGo calendar is embedded within other websites. SpinGo is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. For information regarding the practices of affiliated websites, please review the privacy policies of each of those websites. This privacy policy is restricted to the practices of SpinGo only.

For reasons such as improving member experience and providing customized communications to our users, we may receive information about you from third party sources and our web logs (see the "Web Logs" section below) and add it to the information that we have received from you.

Web logs automatically record anything a web server sees, which may include email addresses you enter into a form or pages viewed by a user at a particular IP address. If you are not a registered user of SpinGo, we will not use the information from web logs to market to you. If you are a registered user of SpinGo, we may use web log information about your use of SpinGo in order to inform you about content, upgrades, or services in accordance with your email options.

With Whom SpinGo Shares Information

We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties, aside from entities that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders or processing payment, that either are bound to comply with our privacy policy or have privacy policies that protect your information. As stated, SpinGo may use third parties to accept and process orders for event upgrades and sponsorships, and such third parties may get access to your personal information for the purposes of providing services or products to you on SpinGo's behalf. 

However, SpinGo may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on SpinGo; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of SpinGo; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety.

We may request demographic information from you (for example, your age, education level or household income) from time to time. We will not share that information in a manner that identifies you as an individual with any other entity, unless we let you know that at the time of collection or we have your permission. When we share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only.

In the event that ownership of SpinGo were to change, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party so services may continue. In the event of such a transfer, your personal information would remain subject to the practices designated in the pre-existing privacy policy.

Information Regarding Minors

SpinGo.com is a general audience site and is not directed to children under the age of 13. SpinGo assumes products purchased through credit card means are purchased by adults. SpinGo respects the privacy of parents and children and is committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). 

If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to SpinGo, he or she can contact us via e-mail at privacy [at] spingo.com. SpinGo will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived in web logs and back-up archives after SpinGo deletes the information from its active database (see the Web Logs paragraph above, and the Archived Information paragraph below).

SpinGo believes that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission.

Other Information

If you elect to use our invitation service for informing a friend about our site or a specific event, we will ask you to provide information needed to send this invitation, such as your friend's name and email address. SpinGo will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to visit the SpinGo calendar. SpinGo stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this email. Your friend may contact us at privacy [at] spingo.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

SpinGo maintains archives of its web logs, database, and other systems and information. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived after SpinGo deletes the information from its active database (see the Web Logs paragraph above). SpinGo maintains archives for disaster recovery, legal and other non-marketing purposes.

You can help SpinGo maintain the accuracy of your profile by notifying us when you change your name or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to update your information, sign in to SpinGo and update your user information.
